Physical fitness is all about cardio exercises and weightlifting… right?
体能训练就是有氧运动和举重……
If you've ever finished a run and then jumped straight into the rest of your day without stretching, only to wake up the next day feeling stiff and with aching muscles, then listen up.
对吧？如果你曾跑完步后没有拉伸就直接进入一天的其余活动，结果第二天醒来感到身体僵硬、肌肉酸痛，那么请听好。
Flexibility plays a big role in our lives – even bending down to pick something up off the floor requires flexibility – but it's often ignored and neglected.
柔韧性在我们的生活中扮演着重要角色——即使是弯腰捡起地上的东西也需要柔韧性——但它常常被忽视和忽略。
So, why and how should we stretch?
那么，我们为什么要拉伸，又该如何拉伸呢？
When athletes stretch, it's not just for show, they do it to prevent injury.
当运动员拉伸时，不仅仅是为了表演，他们这样做是为了预防受伤。
A review of research called 'Effects of Stretching on Injury Risk Reduction and Balance' highlighted that stretching not only reduces injury risk by improving the flexibility of the muscles, it also improves balance, which reduces the risk of falls and those associated injuries.
一项名为《拉伸对降低受伤风险和改善平衡的影响》的研究综述强调，拉伸不仅通过提高肌肉的柔韧性来降低受伤风险，还能改善平衡，从而降低跌倒及相关伤害的风险。
Stretching can also help maintain good posture by keeping our muscles long and loose, which is especially important if you spend hours hunched over a desk.
拉伸还可以通过保持肌肉的舒展和松弛来帮助维持良好的姿势，如果你长时间弓背伏案工作，这一点尤其重要。
In the modern world, many of us spend a large proportion of our days sitting, which can lead to chronic pain, particularly in the neck and shoulders.
在现代社会，我们许多人一天中大部分时间都坐着，这可能导致慢性疼痛，尤其是在颈部和肩部。
Stretching can alleviate this tension and boost blood circulation.
拉伸可以缓解这种紧张并促进血液循环。
What's the best way to reap these benefits?
获得这些益处的最佳方式是什么？
While stretching advice varies, the ACSM's Health & Fitness Journal provides guidelines which include stretching the major muscle groups such as the hamstrings and quadriceps at least two or three times per week.
尽管拉伸建议各不相同，但美国运动医学会的《健康与健身杂志》提供了指导原则，包括每周至少拉伸主要肌群（如腘绳肌和股四头肌）两到三次。
A 2017 review of research, published in the Sports Med journal, suggests that dynamic stretches, where you stretch in slow, repeated movements, have greater benefits in a pre-exercise warm-up than static stretches, where you hold a pose.
2017年发表在《运动医学》期刊上的一项研究综述表明，在运动前热身时，动态拉伸（以缓慢、重复的动作进行拉伸）比静态拉伸（保持一个姿势）更有益。
Stretching is better after a quick warm-up because the muscle is more pliable, reducing the risk of muscle strains.
在快速热身后进行拉伸效果更好，因为此时肌肉更具柔韧性，从而降低肌肉拉伤的风险。
Stretching isn't just for athletes and fitness lovers.
拉伸不仅仅是运动员和健身爱好者的专利。"
"Stretching is also an accessible way to unwind and destress during or after a busy day," says Jessica Matthews, professor of kinesiology and author of 'Stretching to Stay Young'.
在忙碌的一天中间或结束后，拉伸也是一种方便的放松和减压方式，"运动机能学教授、《拉伸保持年轻》一书的作者杰西卡·马修斯说。
So why not finish the day relaxing in a child's pose, a spinal twist or a happy baby?
那么，为什么不以婴儿式、脊柱扭转式或快乐婴儿式来放松地结束一天呢？